Little Magazine Collection, 1895-1976 (bulk 1965-1976)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Occident, University of California, Berkeley, California, v. 4, Spring/Summer, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- Occult, Tampa, Florida, #1, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 27)
- Oculist Witnesses, Dorchester, Massachusetts, #2, Winter, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 28)
- Odda Tala, Palo Alto, California, #2, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Odysseus, Portland, Oregon, v. 1, #2, October, 1971-November, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Odysseus, Portland, Oregon, v. 1, #4, February, 1972-May, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Odyssey, Chicago, v. 1, #1, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Odyssey, Chicago, v. 1, #3, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Odyssey, Richmond, Virginia, v. 1, December, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Odyssey, Richmond, Virginia, v. 1, March, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Oink!, Chicago, #1, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Oink!, Chicago, #2, January, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Oink!, Chicago, #3, May, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Oink!, Chicago, #4, August, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Oink!, Chicago, #5, December, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Oink!, Chicago, #6, May, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Olson, University of Connecticut Library, Storrs, Connecticut, #5, Spring, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Olson, University of Connecticut Library, Storrs, Connecticut, #6, Fall, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Olympia, Paris, France, #1, January, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Olympia, Paris, France, #3, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Olympia, Paris, France, #4, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- One, Cheadle Hulme, England, #1, Summer, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- 100 Flowers Review, Cambridge, Massachusetts, v. 1, #1, November, 1974-December, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- 100 Flowers Review, Cambridge, Massachusetts, v. 1, #2, January, 1975-February, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- 100 Flowers Review, Cambridge, Massachusetts, v. 1, #3, March, 1975-April, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Onslaught, Pepper Pike, Ohio, #1, April 21, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- The Open Cell, Berkeley, California, v. 1, #1, August, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Open Letter, Victoria, Canada, #5, November, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Open Letter, Toronto, Canada, #1 (2nd series), Winter, 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Open Letter, Toronto, Canada, #2, Summer, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Open Letter, Toronto, Canada, #3, Fall, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Open Letter, Toronto, Canada, #4, Spring, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Open Places, New York City, #1, November, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Open Places, Columbia, Missouri, #5, May, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Open Places, Columbia, Missouri, #6, September, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Open Places, Columbia, Missouri, #11, January, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Open Places, Columbia, Missouri, #12-13, May, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Open Places, Columbia, Missouri, #14, Winter, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Open Places, Columbia, Missouri, #19, Spring/Summer, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Open Places, Columbia, Missouri, #20, Fall/Winter, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Open Places, Columbia, Missouri, #22, Fall/Winter, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Open Reading, Rohnert Park, California, #1 (2nd series), March, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Open Reading, Rohnert Park, California, #2, Fall, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Open Reading, Rohnert Park, California, #3, Spring, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- openspaces, Los Angeles, v. 1, #1, Spring, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Open Window, #2, Fall, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Ophir, Pretoria, South Africa, #8, April, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Opium, Argentina, v. 2, #2, June, 1965-July, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Opus, Mexico, #3, circa June, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Opus, California Western Campus, U.S. International University, San Diego, #7, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Opus, California Western Campus, U.S. International University, San Diego, #9, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Or, San Francisco, v. 1, #1, August 13, 1975-April 14, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Or, San Francisco, v. 1, #2, August 13, 1975-April 14, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Or, San Francisco, v. 1, #3, August 13, 1975-April 14, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Or, San Francisco, v. 1, #4, August 13, 1975-April 14, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Or, San Francisco, v. 1, #5, August 13, 1975-April 14, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Or, San Francisco, v. 1, #6, August 13, 1975-April 14, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Or, San Francisco, v. 1, #7, August 13, 1975-April 14, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Or, San Francisco, v. 1, #8, August 13, 1975-April 14, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Or, San Francisco, v. 1, #9, August 13, 1975-April 14, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Or, San Francisco, v. 1, #10, August 13, 1975-April 14, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Or, San Francisco, v. 1, #11, August 13, 1975-April 14, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Or, San Francisco, v. 1, #12, August 13, 1975-April 14, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Or, San Francisco, v. 1, #13, August 13, 1975-April 14, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Or, San Francisco, v. 1, #14, August 13, 1975-April 14, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Or, San Francisco, v. 1, #15, August 13, 1975-April 14, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Orfeo, Chili, #21-22, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- oriental blue streak, Placitas, New Mexico, Spring, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Origin, Dorchester, Massachusetts, #2, Summer, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Origin, Dorchester, Massachusetts, #3, Fall, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Origin, Dorchester, Massachusetts, #15, Winter/Spring, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Origin, Dorchester, Massachusetts, #19, Summer, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Origin, Kyoto, Japan, #2 (series 3), July, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Origin, Kyoto, Japan, #6, July, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Origin, Kyoto, Japan, #7, October, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Origin, Kyoto, Japan, #8, January, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- Out of Sight, San Francisco, v. 1, #2, August 1, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #1, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #2, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #3, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 29)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #4, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #5, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 31)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #6, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 32)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #7, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 33)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #8, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 34)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #9, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 35)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #10, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 36)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #11, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 37)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #12, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 38)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #13, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 39)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #14, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 40)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #15, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 41)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #16, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 42)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #17, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 43)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #18, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 44)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #19, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 45)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #20, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 46)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #21, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 47)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #22, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 48)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #23, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 49)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #24, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 50)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #25, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 51)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #26, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 52)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #27, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 53)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #28, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 54)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #29, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 55)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #30, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 56)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #31, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 57)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #32, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 58)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #33, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 59)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #34, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 60)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #35, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 61)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #36, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 62)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #37, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 63)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #38, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 64)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #39, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 65)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #40, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 66)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #41, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 67)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #42, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 68)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #43, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 69)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #44, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 70)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #45, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 71)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #46, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 72)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #47, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 73)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #48, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 74)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #49, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 75)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #50, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 76)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #51, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 77)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #52, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 78)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #53, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 79)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #54, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 80)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #55, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 81)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #56, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 82)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #57, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 83)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #58, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 84)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #59, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 85)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #60, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 86)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #61, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 87)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #62, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 88)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #63, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 89)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #64, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 90)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #65, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 91)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #66, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 92)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #67, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 93)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #13 (new series), June, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 94)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #20, December, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 95)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #21, December, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 96)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #23, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 97)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #24, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 98)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #27, November, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 99)
- Out of Sight, Wichita, Kansas, #28, January, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 100)
- Out There, Chicago, #2, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 101)
- Out There, Chicago, #10, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 102)
- Outerbridge, Staten Island Community College, Staten Island, New York, v. 1, #1, Spring, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Outlet, Manhattan, Kansas, v. 1, #1, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Overflow, Ann Arbor, Michigan, v. 1, #3, Spring, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Overflow, Ann Arbor, Michigan, v. 2, #2, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Overflow, Ann Arbor, Michigan, v. 2, #3, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- The Owl, University of Santa Clara, Santa Clara, California, v. 49, #1, Fall, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Oyez!, Roosevelt University, Chicago, v. 2, #1, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Oyez!, Roosevelt University, Chicago, v. 8, #1 (Oyez Review), 1973 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- P M Newsletter, Blackburn, England, #19, Summer, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- PN2 experiment, Sacramento, California, #2, undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
- PN2 experiment, Sacramento, California, #3, undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
- PN2 experiment, Scranton, Pennsylvania, #4, undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
- PN2 experiment, Scranton, Pennsylvania, #5, undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
- PN2 experiment, Scranton, Pennsylvania, #6, undated (Box 35, Folder 14)
- PN2 experiment, Sacramento, California, #7, undated (Box 35, Folder 15)
- PN2 experiment, Sacramento, California, #10, undated (Box 35, Folder 16)
- PN2 experiment, Sacramento, California, #11, undated (Box 35, Folder 17)
- P. V. P., Philadelphia, v. 1, #4, July, 1965-August, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Pacific, Mills College, Oakland, California, v. 1, #1, November, 1945 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Pacific, Mills College, Oakland, California, v. 1, #2, January, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Pacific Nation, Vancouver, Canada, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Pacific Nation, Vancouver, Canada, #2, February, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- Pacific Review, Goleta, California, v. 1, #1, Spring, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- Pages, Berkhansted, England, #1, Autumn, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- Paintbrush, Laramie, Wyoming, #4, Autumn, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- The Painted Bride Quarterly, Philadelphia, v. 3, #4, Winter, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- Pa'Lante, New York City, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 27)
- Pan, New York City/Housatonic, Massachusetts, #2, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 28)
- The Pan American Review, Edingburg, Texas, v. 1, #1, Winter, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Panache, New York City, v. 1, #1, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Panache, New York City, #2, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Panache, New York City, Summer, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Panache, Princeton, New Jersey, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Panache, Princeton, New Jersey, #8, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Panache, Princeton, New Jersey, #9, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Panache, Princeton, New Jersey, #11, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Panache, Princeton, New Jersey, #12, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Panache, Princeton, New Jersey, #13, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Panjandrum, San Francisco, #2-3, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Panjandrum, San Francisco, #4, Fall, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Paper Pudding, Monte Rio, California, #4, Spring, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Paper Pudding, Monte Rio, California, #5, Autumn, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- The Paris Magazine, Paris, France, #1, October, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- The Park, London, England, #4-5, Summer, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Participation-Poesia, Panama, #1, September, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- La Pata de Palo, Venezuela, #4, May, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- La Pata de Palo, Venezuela, #5, November, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Pathways, Vacaville, California, v. 4, #1, Spring, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Paunch, Buffalo, New York, #31, April, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Paunch, Buffalo, New York, #32, August, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Pebble, Slippery Rock, Pennsylvania, v. 1, #1, Autumn, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Pebble, Slippery Rock, Pennsylvania, v. 1, #2, Spring, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Pembroke Magazine, Pembroke State University, Pembroke, North Carolina, #5, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Pen Rejects, #3, July, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Penelope, Panama, #6, December, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- The Pendulum of Time and the Arts, Glendale, New York, v. 13, #83, May, 1969-June, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- The Pendulum of Time and the Arts, Glendale, New York, v. 13, #84, July, 1969-August, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #23, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #45, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #46, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #47, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #48, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #49, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #50, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #51, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #53, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #54, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #55, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #56, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #57, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #58, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #59, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #60, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #61, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #62, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #64, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 26)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #65, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #66, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #67, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 29)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #68, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #69, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 31)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #70, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 32)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #71, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 33)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #72, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 34)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #73, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 35)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #74, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 36)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #77, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 37)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #78, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 38)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #83, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 39)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #84, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 40)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #85, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 41)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #86, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 42)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #89, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 43)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #92, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 44)
- Penny Poems, New Haven, Connecticut, #93, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 45)
- Penny Poems from Midwestern University, Wichita Falls, Texas, v. 3, #1-10, March 14, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 46)
- Penny Poems from Midwestern University, Wichita Falls, Texas, v. 4, #1-10, April 30, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 47)
- Penny Poems from Midwestern University, Wichita Falls, Texas, v. 5, #1-10, October 30, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 48)
- Penny Poems from Midwestern University, Wichita Falls, Texas, v. 6, #1-10, April 15, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 49)
- Penny Poems from Midwestern University, Wichita Falls, Texas, v. 7, #1-10, November 16, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 50)
- Penumbra, New York City, v. 1, #5, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 51)
- Penumbra, New York City, #6, July, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 52)
- Penumbra, New York City, #7, December, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 53)
- Penumbra, New York City, #8, July, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 54)
- Penumbra, New York City, #9, February, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 55)
- Penumbra, New York City, #10, Fall, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 56)
- Penumbra, New York City, #11, Fall, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 57)
- Pequod, Forest Knolls, California, v. 1, #1, Spring, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 58)
- Pequod, University of San Diego, San Diego, California, #2, Spring, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 59)
- Perfiles Poeticos de los Paises Latinos/Profils Poetiques des Pays Latins, Mexico/France, January, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 60)
- Perspectives, London/New York City, #6, Winter, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 61)
- Perspectives, London/New York City, #10, Winter, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 62)
- Perspectives, London/New York City, #11, Spring, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 63)
- Perspectives, London/New York City, #12, Summer, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 64)
- Perspectives, San Francisco, v. 1, #1, October, 1965-November, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 65)
- Perspectives, San Francisco, v. 1, #3, February, 1966-March, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 66)
- Perspectives, San Francisco, #4, April, 1966-May, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 67)
- Phantasm, Chico, California, v. 1, #3, May, 1976-June, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Phoebe, George Mason University, Fairfax, Virginia, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Phoebe, George Mason University, Fairfax, Virginia, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- The Phoenix, Haydenville, Massachusetts, v. 3, #1, Winter, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- The Phoenix, Haydenville, Massachusetts, v. 3, #4, Autumn, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Phoenix, Manchester, England, #6-7, Summer, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Phoenix, San Francisco, v. 1, #1, September 13, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Pine Knots, Northern Arizona University, Flagstaff, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Pine Knots, Northern Arizona University, Flagstaff, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Pine Knots, Northern Arizona University, Flagstaff, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Plainsong, Minneapolis, #2, Spring, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Pliego, Orono, Maine, #1, undated (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Pliego, Orono, Maine, #9, undated (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Pliego, Orono, Maine, #10, undated (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Pliego, Orono, Maine, #12, undated (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Pliego, Orono, Maine, #16, undated (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Pliego, Orono, Maine, #17, undated (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Pliego, Orono, Maine, #23-26, undated (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Pliego, Milwaukie, Oregon, #33, undated (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Pliego, Milwaukie, Oregon, #34, undated (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Pliego, Milwaukie, Oregon, #35, undated (Box 38, Folder 21)
- Pluck, University of Alberta, Edmonton, Canada, v. 1, #1, January, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Pluck, University of Alberta, Edmonton, Canada, v. 1, #2, Spring, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Pluck, University of Alberta, Edmonton, Canada, v. 2, #1, Fall (#3), 1968 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Ploughshares, Cambridge, Massachusetts, v. 3, #2, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Podium, Cleveland, Ohio, v. 1, #1, July, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Podium, Cleveland, Ohio, v. 1, #2, October, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Poem, Huntsville, Alabama, v. 1, November, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- Poems & Pictures, San Francisco, #1, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 29)
- Poems & Pictures, San Francisco, #2, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 30)
- Poems from the Floating World, New York City, v. 5, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 31)
- Poesia Paraguaya Hoy, Paraguay, v. 2, #5, March, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Poesia Vivante, Switzerland, #17-18, February, 1966-March, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Poesia Vivante, Switzerland, #30, circa 1969 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Poet, Madras, India, v. 7, #4, June, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Poet, Madras, India, v. 10, #4, April, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Poetmeat, Blackburn, England, #9-10, Summer, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Poetmeat, Blackburn, England, #11, Summer, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Poetmeat, Blackburn, England, #12, Autumn, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Poetmeat, Blackburn, England, #13, undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Poetry and Audience, Leeds University, Leeds, England, v. 19, #3, January, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Poetry and Audience, Leeds University, Leeds, England, v. 19, #4, February, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Poetry and Audience, Leeds University, Leeds, England, v. 19, #6, March, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Poetry and Audience, Leeds University, Leeds, England, v. 19, #7, April, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Poetry and Audience, Leeds University, Leeds, England, v. 20, #1, October, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Poetry Florida and..., DeLand, Florida, v. 1, #3-4, Spring/Summer, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Poetry Florida and..., DeLand, Florida, v. 2, #1, Fall (#5), 1968 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Poetry Florida and..., DeLand, Florida, v. 2, #2, Spring (#6), 1969 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Poetry Folios, Barnet, England, Summer, 1943 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Poetry Folios, Barnet, England, #4, Autumn, 1943 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Poetry Folios, Barnet, England, #7, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Poetry India, Bombay, India, v. 1, #2, April, 1966-June, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Poetry India, Bombay, India, v. 1, #3, July, 1966-September, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Poetry London-New York, New York City, v. 1, #1, March, 1956-April, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Poetry London-New York, New York City, v. 1, #2, Winter, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Poetry London-New York, New York City, v. 1, #3, Winter, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 25)